const animals = [{"question":"Three of these animals hibernate. Which one does not?","category":"animals","answer":"Sloth","choices":["Mouse","Sloth","Frog","Snake"]},{"question":"All of these animals are omnivorous except one.","category":"animals","answer":"Snail","choices":["Fox","Mouse","Opossum","Snail"]},{"question":"Three of these Latin names are names of bears. Which is the odd one?","category":"animals","answer":"Felis silvestris catus","choices":["Melursus ursinus","Helarctos malayanus","Ursus minimus","Felis silvestris catus"]},{"question":"These are typical Australian animals except one.","category":"animals","answer":"Sloth","choices":["Platypus","Dingo","Echidna","Sloth"]},{"question":"Representatives of three of these species produce venom of their own. Which is the odd species?","category":"animals","answer":"Mosquitos","choices":["Lizards","Scorpions","Frogs","Mosquitos"]},{"question":"Three of these species shed their skin. Which one does not?","category":"animals","answer":"Penguins","choices":["Penguins","Snakes","Insects","Crustaceans"]},{"question":"All dogs, cats and birds are colorblind.","category":"animals","answer":"False","choices":["True","False"]},{"question":"All of these animals have large ears (relative to their size) except one.","category":"animals","answer":"Polar bears","choices":["Polar bears","Foxes","Bats","Elephants"]},{"question":"This percentage of all snakes on Earth are lethal to humans.","category":"animals","answer":"15%","choices":["10%","20%","15%","25%"]},{"question":"Snakes are this kind of animals.","category":"animals","answer":"Carnivorous","choices":["Herbivorous","Omnivorous","Carnivorous","Vegetarian"]},{"question":"Snakes consume their food by means of this process.","category":"animals","answer":"Swallowing","choices":["Breathing","Absorption","Swallowing","Chewing"]},{"question":"Snakes reproduce only by laying eggs.","category":"animals","answer":"False","choices":["True","False"]},{"question":"Snakes are deaf.","category":"animals","answer":"True","choices":["True","False"]},{"question":"Snake skin is covered in scales.","category":"animals","answer":"True","choices":["True","False"]},{"question":"Snakes belong to the following category.","category":"animals","answer":"Reptiles","choices":["Invertebrates","Lizards","Reptiles","Mammals"]},{"question":"A specialist in snakes is called one of these.","category":"animals","answer":"Ophiologist","choices":["Pisciculturist","Ornithologist","Ophiologist","Herpetologist"]},{"question":"One of the following snakes does not belong to the Viperidae family.","category":"animals","answer":"Grass snake","choices":["Horned adder","Grass snake","Viper","Asp"]},{"question":"Snakes are very likely to attack us, regardless of whether they feel threatened or not.","category":"animals","answer":"False","choices":["True","False"]},{"question":"Cobras are venomous snakes of family Elapidae, that generally inhabit regions of these two continents.","category":"animals","answer":"Asia and Africa","choices":["South America and Asia","Asia and Africa","Asia and Australia","South America and Australia"]},{"question":"The cobras most recognizable feature is its hood, a flap of skin and muscle behind the head, believed to serve this purpose.","category":"animals","answer":"More threatening appearance","choices":["Balance control","Heat collection from sun rays","Camouflage","More threatening appearance"]},{"question":"The Cobra is at the top of the food chain, with only two main predators -- one is man and the other is this animal.","category":"animals","answer":"Mongoose","choices":["Jackal","Mongoose","Lynx","Eagle"]},{"question":"This is where the Cobras ribs are situated.","category":"animals","answer":"Behind its head","choices":["Behind its head","In its chest, around the middle of the body","Cobras have no ribs","In its tale"]},{"question":"The King Cobra feeds almost exclusively on other snakes, even toxic ones.","category":"animals","answer":"True","choices":["True","False"]},{"question":"A baby cobra is fully able to defend itself in as little as this many hours after being born.","category":"animals","answer":"3","choices":["3","12","48","72"]},{"question":"What type of dog did Richard Nixon receive from a Texan while he was a candidate for Vice President?","category":"animals","answer":"Cocker Spaniel","choices":["German Shepherd","Cocker Spaniel","Golden Retriever","Welsh Corgy"]},{"question":"What was the name of Socks companion at the White House during the Clinton Administration?","category":"animals","answer":"Buddy","choices":["Buddy","Shoes","Bailey","Buster"]},{"question":"President Fords dog was named Freedom.","category":"animals","answer":"False","choices":["False","True"]},{"question":"Which of these Presidents had the most pets?","category":"animals","answer":"Theodore Roosevelt","choices":["Franklin Delano Roosevelt","Theodore Roosevelt","Bill Clinton","Woodrow Wilson"]},{"question":"What breed is known as the favourite breed of Queen Elizabeth II?","category":"animals","answer":"Welsh Corgi","choices":["Border Collie","Old English Sheepdog","Welsh Corgi","Australian Cattle Dog"]},{"question":"What was the name of Fraisers fathers dog on the hit TV show set in Seattle?","category":"animals","answer":"Eddie","choices":["Niles","Marty","Eddie","Skip"]},{"question":"Which one of these sea mammals is not in the endangered species lists?","category":"animals","answer":"Pilot whale","choices":["Fin Whale","Pilot whale","Blue Whale","Humpback Whale"]},{"question":"This endangered turtle is the biggest of all living turtles, reaching a length of over 2.7 m (8.8 ft) and weight of 900 kg (2,000 lb).","category":"animals","answer":"Leatherback Sea Turtle","choices":["Leatherback Sea Turtle","Kemps Ridley Turtle","Hawksbill Sea Turtle","Mesoamerican River Turtle"]},{"question":"Name the rarest and most endangered of all wolves.","category":"animals","answer":"Red Wolf","choices":["Red Wolf","Ethiopian Wolf","Black-backed Wolf","Gray Wolf"]},{"question":"The endangered Komodo dragon is the largest living lizard in the world, growing to an average length of 2-3 meters (10 feet).","category":"animals","answer":"True","choices":["False","True"]},{"question":"This species of great apes with long arms and reddish hair suffer habitat destruction due to logging, mining and forest fires.","category":"animals","answer":"Orangutan","choices":["Gorilla","Baboons","Orangutan","Chimpanzee"]},{"question":"What is the natural habitat of the snows leopard, that was hunted down for its beautiful fur, as a result of which its population went down to 1,000 animals in the 1960s?","category":"animals","answer":"Central Asia","choices":["North America","Central Asia and North America","Central Asia","Europe and North America"]},{"question":"The Asian Elephant, the only living species of the genus Elephas, is the bigger relative of the African Elephant.","category":"animals","answer":"False","choices":["True","False"]},{"question":"This freshwater mammal, found only in the Yangtze River, is the most endangered (even possibly extinct) cetacean and one of the most endangered species in the world.","category":"animals","answer":"Chinese River Dolphin","choices":["Ganges River Dolphin","Chinese River Dolphin","La Plata Dolphin","Amazon River Dolphin"]},{"question":"This small nocturnal animal, whose natural habitat are the deserts of Northern Africa, is known to jump not only for hunting or protection, but also for pleasure.","category":"animals","answer":"Fennec","choices":["Cape Fox","Red Fox","Bengal Fox","Fennec"]},{"question":"Jack jumper ants, yellowish-orange carnivorous ants named after their characteristic jumpy motions, can be found only on which continent?","category":"animals","answer":"Australia","choices":["North America","Australia","Africa","Asia"]},{"question":"This small, graceful member of the antelope family is an extraordinary jumper - while leaping, it touches the rocky terrain of its South African habitats only with the tip of its hooves, resembling a dance.","category":"animals","answer":"Klipspringer","choices":["Oribi","Roan Antelope","Scimitar Oryx","Klipspringer"]},{"question":"Although the jumping viper, a chiefly nocturnal snake, is one of the most powerful jumpers of the snake family, capable of rising up to 1 meter (3 feet) during a strike, its poison is not lethal to humans.","category":"animals","answer":"False","choices":["False","True"]},{"question":"Zoophobia is the fear of animals.","category":"animals","answer":"True","choices":["True","False"]},{"question":"The hummingbird is the worlds smallest bird.","category":"animals","answer":"True","choices":["False","True"]},{"question":"Which of these animals swims the fastest?","category":"animals","answer":"Dolphin","choices":["Flounder","Shark","Dolphin","Jellyfish"]},{"question":"Which word refers to the sound peacocks make?","category":"animals","answer":"Scream","choices":["Scream","Squill","Squeak","Squall"]},{"question":"Ancient Japanese thought this animal caused earthquakes.","category":"animals","answer":"Spiders","choices":["Birds","Spiders","Snakes","Frogs"]},{"question":"How many types of bats are there?","category":"animals","answer":"900","choices":["900","700","500","200"]}]